# YOHANNES NABABAN

# UI/UX DESIGNER

It is happy to evaluate and redesign a website or application in order to produce a product that has the usability, ease and satisfaction of a good user experience. Committed to making a big impact on the progress of the company I work for.



- Cluster Griya Pancoran Blok A1, Rangkapan Jaya Baru, Pancoran Mas, Depok City
- 082245276374
- yohannesn24.yn@gmail.com
- Bē yohannesnababan
- in Yohannes Nababan

## EDUCATION BACKGROUND

#### **Del Institute of Techonology**

BACHELOR OF INFORMATIC 2016

• Maintained a 3.18 GPA all 8 semesters

## CERTIFICATIONS

- UI Design Specialization
- Human Computer Interaction
- The Practical Guide to Usability
- Empathy in UX Design
- UX Designer from Scratch
- UX Research for Agile Teams



#### SPECIALIZATIONS

- User Experience Designer
- User Interface Designer
- Automation Testing
- Manual Testing

#### TOOLS









#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Software Tester Internship

PT. TELKOM INDONESIA
JUNE 2019 TO AGUSTUS 2019

- Manual Testing of several websites belonging to Telkom Indonesia
- Automation testing of several websites belonging to Telkom Indonesia using Katalon Studio
- Performance Testing of several websites belonging to Telkom Indonesia using Jmeter

## ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

### Member of Del Student Choir

DEL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY 2016 - 2018

#### Member of Communication and Information Division

HIMPUNAN MAHASISWA TEKNIK INFORMATIKA 2017 - 2018

#### Voluntary at Toba Enterpreneurship Festival

DEL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY 2017 - 2018